thewiire.com 2010-04-05

# Privacy Policy

---  
  
_Last updated April 2, 2010_

At The Wiire, we strive to bring readers current and accurate news, information, and media relating to the Nintendo Wii. The Wiire is not endorsed, sponsored, nor otherwise affiliated with Nintendo. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use our services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it. If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, you may contact us [here](http://thewiire.com/contact).

### Data Collection

  * **The Wiire will never rent, share, or sell any information you provide to us with any other people, websites, or companies, unless compelled to by law.**
  * The Wiire, its forums, and other website services do not collect any personally identifiable information when viewing in a read-only mode.
  * The Wiire automatically collects limited non-personally identifying information your web browser makes available whenever you visit a page on our website. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your web browser. We use this information only to develop and improve our services.
  * Some of our website services require you to register for a free account. By registering for an account, users are granted the privilege to post their own information, comments, and opinions onto our message boards, provided that they follow the Terms of Service.

### The Wiire Website Account

  * When registering for an [account](http://boards.thewiire.com/index.php?act=Reg&CODE=00), the following information is required: a username, a password, and a valid e-mail address. Your e-mail address can be optionally used for administrative contact, and for contact from other site members. You can choose whether to receive such e-mails from administrators or site members during the registration process.
  * Registering for a website account does not grant the user unlimited or unrestricted access to The Wiire. Certain administrative functions are hidden for security purposes, and may not be accessed by regular users. Attempting to access or otherwise manipulate these administrative controls will have your account temporarily or permanently suspended. By registering for an account, the user must also comply with the The Wiire Terms of Service (see below).

### The Wiire IRC Chatroom

  * The Wiire has an IRC channel available for members and guests to chat live with each other. A Wiire Account is not required to use this service, but a computer with either Flash or an independent IRC client installed is.
  * All of the rules in The Wiire Terms of Service apply to this chatroom. Any user spamming, insulting, or otherwise being disruptive may be kicked and/or banned from the channel.
  * The IRC channel can be either accessed from a standalone IRC client (available at **irc.geekshed.net #thewiire** ), or by visiting [this page](http://www.thewiire.com/irc/ "The Wiire IRC"). (Flash required)

### Intense Debate Comments

  * The Wiire uses a third-party commenting system for the blog posts called Intense Debate.
  * You may see their [terms of service here](http://intensedebate.com/tos "Intense Debate Terms of Service").

### The Wiire Terms of Service

> The Wiire Terms of Service are available [on this page](http://boards.thewiire.com/index.php?act=boardrules).
> 
> The Wiire reserves the right to modify these Terms at any time.

### Information Security

  * We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. 
  * We restrict access to your information to website administrators who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

### Updating Your Information

  * We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information on our services.

### Changes to this Policy

> Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. The latest revision date will be noted at the top of the page.  
  
Last Updated ( Friday, 02 April 2010 17:25 )
